<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>W3C Internationalization Working Group-relevant MDN issues</title>
        <link>https://dontcallmedom.github.io/mdn-issue-by-spec/w3c_internationalization_working_group.rss</link>
        <description>Issue filed on MDN Web Docs related to pages attached to technologies developed by W3C Internationalization Working Group</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 04:15:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[encoding] Content suggestion: ImageDecoder & ImageTrackList how-to/tutorial]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/mdn/content/issues/12791</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/mdn/content/issues/12791</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 04:15:29 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="auto">What is the new suggestion?</h2>
<p dir="auto">Webcodecs introduce ImageDecoder and ImageDecoder come with ImageTrackList.<br>
It sounds like a nice feature but I can't figure out how to provide an image file containing multiple tracks...<br>
I even never heard about tracks inside an image and google doesn't help me at all with that.</p>
<p dir="auto">ImageTrackList exists so I'm sure it's doable but how to package multiple tracks inside a single image file ?</p>
<h2 dir="auto">Why is it important or useful?</h2>
<p dir="auto">I think it would be a great way to organised assets compared to a spritesheet but I have no idea how to create the multi-tracks-image.  What tool am I suppose to use ?  What would be the format of the file ?</p>
<p dir="auto">"Does it address critical needs in the web industry?"<br>
Probably not but this feature existed in Adobe Flash (the ability to package multiple assets, easy to target, inside a single file) and I really miss it. The idea I could do it again soon with ImageDecoder &amp; ImageTrackList makes me very happy. Please show us a step by step example to create such images .</p>
<p dir="auto">MDN URL: <a href="https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Learn/" rel="nofollow">https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Learn/</a><br>
MDN URL: <a href="https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/TextEncoder" rel="nofollow">https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/TextEncoder</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>